# Jimmy Efendi

UI/UX Design & Frontend Dev

jimmyefendi618857@gmail.com jimmyefendi.vercel.app +62 85271654890 Kab. Bekasi, Jawa Barat, Indonesia

Creative professional and collaborator with 2 years experience in IT and Design. Able to create UI and UX Design Android, iOS, Tablet, and Website with better prototype. A frontend developer who is ready to master multi-platform application development.

# **Work Experience**

### **IT Consultant**

Jun 2024 - Present

Klinik Ria Pilar | Cikarang Utara

Development of a clinical ERM system, display, features and functions for sending medical record data so that it can be integrated with the Satusehat platform, etc.

### **IT Support**

Dec 2023 - Aug 2024

PT. Profaskes Softech Indonesia | Bukittinggi

Providing training on system usage to clients, helping clients overcome problems and errors in the system, helping to submit bridging to BPJS Kesehatan and Satusehat Platform, performing database backups, optimizing servers on VPS, etc.

#### **UI/UX Design**

Jul 2022 - Dec 2022

PT. Cipta Tekno Mandiri | Padang

Create brand design and application logo, conduct user research, design user interface (UI) and user experience (UX), create application design for web, android, ios and tablet, create mockup and wireframe, create prototype design, etc.

### **Projects**

#### **Inventory Management System (IMS)**

Android-based application for managing stock in the warehouse, incoming goods, outgoing goods, transactions, etc.

### **Absencio App**

Android-based application for employee attendance such as government agencies, private companies equipped with face recognition features and other features.

#### Sellerku App

Android and iOS based applications in Tablet or iPad versions. Sellerku is a cashier application which is one application for managing many store branches

### **Core Skills**

html, css, javascript, php, lavarel, boostrap, figma, corel, canva, illustrator, photoshop, xd, office, etc.

#### **Education**

### **Universitas Esa Unggul**

Sep 2024 - Present

S2 Master of Computer Science

### Politeknik Negeri Padang

Aug 2019 - Dec 2024

**D4** Software Engineering

## Languages

Indonesia Malaysia

**English**